# **ZAHRA ATAEI**

#### **Nutritionist and Dietitian**

② zataei7474@gmail.com in Zahra Ataei +46 73-780 35 46
AtaHealth

Stockholm, Sweden



### **SUMMARY**

I am an enthusiastic dietitian with more than five years of education and experience in nutrition and dietetics. Currently studying Master's in Nutrition Science at Karolinska Institutet.

I have helped patients with various health problems. This experience has given me the ability to think critically to deal with different situations. I work based on scientific evidence, and I am skilled at consulting people to have healthy lifestyles. Reliability and having a great sense of responsibility are my strengths at work.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Nutrition Coach**

at social media

## Jul, 2020 - Ongoing

Stockholm, Sweden

As I have concerns about public health issues, especially in developing counties, I have created social media pages to inform, consult, and inspire people to have healthy eating habits and lifestyles. My page on Instagram now has more than 10,000 followers, mostly Persian-speaking living around the world.

#### **Dietitian**

at Munesi gym

Mov, 2017 - Nov, 2018

♦ Tehran, Iran

I worked there as a dietitian and consultant for beginners and professional trainers as well as obese and overweight people.

#### **Dietitian**

at Freelance

▼ Tehran, Iran

I have worked independently with pregnant and nursing mothers, overweight people, and those with metabolic syndrome as a part-time job. I worked online and was able to assist many individuals in improving their health.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Masters' in Nutrition Science**

at Karolinska Institutet

Aug, 2021 - Ongoing

Stockholm, Sweden

#### **Bachelors' in Nutrition and Dietetics**

## **SKILLS**

Flexibility and adaptability

Communication

Microsoft PowerPoint

Nutrition coaching

Lifestyle intervention

Diet management

Collaboration with other healthcare professionals

Nutrition status assessment

Nutrition needs assessment

## **LANGUAGES**

Swedish: C1

English: B2

Persian: Native

## **INTERNSHIPS**

### various departments

at Shahid Beheshti Hospital

may, 2017 - May, 2018

- Hospital's food department
- Medical diagnostic laboratory
- · Children's disease department
- · Health center
- · Liver, Digestive and Pancreatic Department
- Cardiovascular CCU Department
- · Department of Diabetes and Endocrinology
- · Surgery and ICU
- · Kidney department
- · The food industry and municipalities

I have passed all the practices with good grades.

## **REFERENCES**

#### Dr. Zatollah Asemi (Professor)

from Kashan University of Medical Sciences

e-post: asemi\_r@yahoo.com

## **HOBBIES**

Exercise
Cycling
Traveling
Camping
Hiking
Blogging
Baking and cooking
Listening to podcasts
Reading books
Reading scientific articles